{
    "subject": "resource/Oldenburg_Academy_of_the_Immaculate_Conception",
    "predicate": "ontology/city",
    "object": "resource/Oldenburg,_Indiana",
    "human_readable": "Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception is located in Oldenburg, Indiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9823547601699829,
            "question": "Where is the Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9441910982131958,
            "question": "What is the name of the academy located in Oldenburg, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9302099347114563,
            "question": "Is the Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception a school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8798794746398926,
            "question": "What state is Oldenburg, Indiana in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8731643557548523,
            "question": "What type of institution is the Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7626569271087646,
            "question": "What might be some extracurricular activities offered at the Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730746328830719,
            "question": "What is the significance of Oldenburg, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856217980384827,
            "question": "What are some historical facts about Oldenburg, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5287710428237915,
            "question": "Does Oldenburg, Indiana have any other notable institutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06627465784549713,
            "question": "Are there any other academies named after saints?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception is located in Oldenburg, Indiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4122_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Oldenburg, Indiana have any other notable institutions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4122_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some historical facts about Oldenburg, Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4122_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Oldenburg, Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4122_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4122_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Oldenburg Academy of the Immaculate Conception is based in Oldenburg, Indiana,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}